What are some maybe some like affirmations to walk out the house with to be a part of making the movement to make?
Yes. OK, how about this? No one is out to get me.
I am enough. No one is out to get me.
No one? No one. Imagine if you grasp that. Marjorie Taylor Greene.
Or let me say this. They may be out to get me, but nobody can get me.
I think that's yeah, because they out to get me. Nobody can get me.
When we expect negativity, that's not true either.
If you believe that somebody is out to get you or you believe that, you know, there's no opportunities coming for you or nobody's going to ever love you.
These are lies. These are lies, too, or things that have not come to fruition yet either.
So why not in this moment choose to believe that good is on its way and that life can change in beautiful ways for me?
There's enough reality that's going to meet us outside the door while I'm in here.
I'm going to make the picture pretty for me. And I suggest you do it for you.